http://www.maggiescrochet.com/pages/privacy-security-notice

Privacy & Security Notice
Maggie Weldon Designs operates web sites which adhere to industry standards in helping to assure our customers' privacy. All information, including transactions, customer accounts, and all correspondence, are handled with discretion and care. The policies below apply to all of the web sites Maggie Weldon Designs owns and operates. By using our web sites, you agree to the collection and use of your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Standards. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our web sites.
Personal Information Collected By Maggie Weldon DesignsWhen you make a purchase on our web site, we request you to provide financial information such as account or credit card numbers. We will use your financial information to bill you for products and services or otherwise process your transactions. By making a purchase on our web site, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction. Maggie Weldon Designs does not and will not ever share or sell your personal information with a third party company.
Your E-mail AddressIf you have provided your e-mail address to Maggie Weldon Designs, you will receive e-mails from us with information and offers from Maggie Weldon Designs. With every commercial e-mail, we will provide you with a link to opt-out from receiving future commercial e-mail. You can also opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages from us by e-mailing us. Opt-out requests are usually handled as soon as the request is made. However, it may take up to ten days to process an opt-out request. Please note that if you elect not to receive commercial e-mail messages from us, we will continue to send you transactional related e-mail, such as product recall information, or safety or security information, subscription information, membership details, account status, order confirmations, shipping confirmations, invoices and customer service related e-mail.
Your PhotosPlease note that by sharing photos with Maggie's Crochet on social media or email, you are agreeing to allow Maggie's Crochet to share the photo on our social media pages, blog, and/or community gallery. We want to celebrate your successes!
Offline Communications from Maggie Weldon DesignWhen you provide your name, address, and telephone number to Maggie Weldon Designs, we may use this information to contact you with correspondence and promotional offers from Maggie's Crochet. You always have the opportunity to choose to no longer receive these communications from us by writing a letter asking us to stop at:
PO Box 2227, Kernersville NC 27284
Security of Your InformationMaggie Weldon Designs values your privacy and the security of your information. We utilize firewalls, secure access storage facilities and other industry standards to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure online commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, to protect the privacy of your information as it travels over the Internet. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.
Changes to this NoticePlease note this Privacy Notice may be changed from time to time. Any changes to this policy will be posted on this page. Please check this page regularly. By using a Maggie Weldon Designs web site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice.
